=Love For Two Lives=
= الحب لعمرين =
=Episode 15=
= الحلقة 15 =
Why are you in my bed?
لماذا انت في سريري
This is my bed.
هذا هو سريري.
What happened?
ماذا حدث؟
You drank too much last night.
لقد شربت كثيرا الليلة الماضية.
You put your arms around me
أنت تضع ذراعيك حولي
and said something
وقال شيئا
quite inappropriate.
غير مناسب تمامًا.
No way.
مستحيل.
W-What did I say?
لم يذكر اسمه: W ماذا قلت؟
You said you wanted to kill me,
قلت أنك تريد قتلي ،
hug me,
احضنّي،
and marry me.
وتزوجني.
And...
و...
It's okay.
حسنا.
This thing can't be known
لا يمكن معرفة هذا الشيء
by anyone
من قبل أي شخص
except the earth,
ما عدا الأرض
the sky,
السماء،
you,
أنت،
and me.
و أنا.
Yeah?
نعم؟
How long have you been there?
كم بقيت هنالك؟
Me?
أنا؟
Just a while.
فقط لبرهة.
You heard everything?
هل سمعت كل شيء؟
I'll go get some cigarettes.
سأذهب لإحضار بعض السجائر.
How can you do this?
كيف يمكنك أن تفعل هذا؟
Do you want breakfast?
هل ترغب في تناول الإفطار؟
Yeah.
نعم.
Okay.
تمام.
I'm off.
أنا خارج.
Oh.
أوه.
Huang Guo'er just came to tell you the Queen Mother asked for you.
جاء هوانغ غوير ليخبرك أن الملكة الأم طلبت منك.
Well...
نحن سوف...
She saw you like that
لقد رأتك هكذا
so she didn't wake you up.
لذلك لم توقظك.
What?
ماذا؟
Like what?
مثل ماذا؟
Wait.
انتظر.
Hey.
يا.
Get this straight.
احصل على هذا مباشرة.
Come back.
عد.
Hey.
يا.
Don't run your mouth.
لا تدير فمك.
Mr. Li.
السيد.  لي.
Safe journey.
رحلة آمنة.
Have a happy life over there.
أتمنى لك حياة سعيدة هناك.
Try to have two kids in three years,
حاول أن تنجب طفلين في غضون ثلاث سنوات ،
and six in five.
وستة من كل خمسة.
Please don't say that.
من فضلك لا تقل ذلك.
Wait.
انتظر.
Why six?
لماذا ستة؟
Twins.
توأمان.
Oh.
أوه.
She must have good fertility.
يجب أن تتمتع بخصوبة جيدة.
Your Majesty.
جلالة الملك.
When a foreign lady marries our court member,
عندما تتزوج سيدة أجنبية عضو المحكمة لدينا ،
she needs to be purified at the Yima Spring
إنها بحاجة إلى التطهير في نبع Yima
and worship the goddess.
وعبادة الآلهة.
The fairy Queen has great power.
الملكة الجنية لديها قوة عظيمة.
You should go with the princess.
يجب أن تذهب مع الأميرة.
Me?
أنا؟
Why do I have to go?
لماذا علي الذهاب؟
What about the chancellor?
ماذا عن المستشار؟
Where is he?
أين هو؟
Isn't that his responsibility?
أليست هذه مسؤوليته؟
The Chancellor saw your great magic power
رأى المستشار قوتك السحرية العظيمة
and felt incompetent.
وشعرت بعدم الكفاءة.
He went back for more training.
عاد لمزيد من التدريب.
General Sa.
العامة سا.
I'll go to the mountain to take a bath.
سأذهب إلى الجبل لأستحم.
We'll go home after.
سوف نعود إلى المنزل بعد.
Wait for me here.
إنتظرني هنا.
Don't worry, Princess.
لا تقلقي يا أميرة.
General Sa will wait for you in the palace after a bath.
عام سوف ينتظرك Sa في القصر بعد الاستحمام.
Let's go, Queen.
دعنا نذهب ، الملكة.
Right away.
حالا.
Aunt.
عمة.
Come back as soon as it's done.
ارجع بمجرد الانتهاء.
Don't worry, Your Majesty.
لا تقلق يا جلالة الملك.
I actually look forward to
أنا في الواقع أتطلع إلى
a random trip like this.
رحلة عشوائية كهذه.
Be careful on the way, Your Majesty.
كن حذرا في الطريق ، جلالة الملك.
I will.
أنا سوف.
Have fun.
استمتع.
Yeah. Let's go.
نعم.  لنذهب.
Princess.
أميرة.
I have a question.
عندي سؤال.
You are so good to General Sa.
أنت جيد جدًا للجنرال سا.
Now he's going so far away to marry.
الآن هو يذهب بعيدا جدا للزواج.
Why do you look so happy?
لماذا تبدو سعيدا جدا؟
Because...
لان...
None of those people are coming back.
لا أحد من هؤلاء الناس يعود.
♪Traces of time and space, and forgotten galaxies♪
آثار الزمان والمكان ، والمجرات المنسية
♪Time alternates our relationship♪
الوقت يتناوب علاقتنا ♪
♪The sea of stars is pretty and quiet♪
♪ بحر النجوم جميل وهادئ
♪The rain touches the breath♪
المطر يمس النفس ♪
♪Get close to you♪
♪ اقترب منك